https://www.silvercity.com.au/privacy-policy/

SEE YOUR PHOTOS
CLICK HERE
SILVERCITY PHOTOS is committed to following best practices in protecting your personal privacy. We hope the following statement outlines clearly how we collect, use and protect the personal information which you provide to us.
Collecting personal information
Information collected or supplied will only be used to process orders or to send information as requested.
We do not use cookies to collect information about how you use our site.
Using your personal information
We only collect your information in order to provide you with information or products, which you request or order. We will only send further information to you in the future if it is requested.
Disclosing your personal information
We will not disclose your personal information to any individual, company or organisation.
We do not share email or address information with other businesses or organisations.
Links
The SILVERCITY PHOTOS web site may provide links to other web sites. These linked sites are not under the control of SILVERCITY PHOTOS and we are not responsible for the conduct of companies or organisations linked to our web site.
Before disclosing your personal information on any other web site, we advise you to examine the Terms and Conditions of those web sites.
About images and photos
Images displayed on our web site are for the purpose of enabling our customers to see and order prints, files or other souvenir photographic products. We will not display any photo that we deem to be defaming, or even unflattering. We may use selected images for promotional purposes.
If you would like to have an image removed from our site simply email or phone us with the title of the image and we will remove it immediately.
Further information
If you have any particular, unusual or sensitive enquiries with regard to privacy matters, phone us on (02) 9552 2402 or email us matt@silvercity.com.au
Contact US
